# **Mohamed Asmeer**

I am a creative Web Developer. I have a strong passion for web development and hands-on experience with WordPress, including theme customization and plugin usage. With a solid foundation in HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript, I possess strong problem-solving skills, attention to detail, and the ability to work independently.

# **Work Experience**

## **Junior Web Developer**

Sri Lanka Railway Department (Jul 2024 - present)

- Developed a Seat Booking System using PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Designed a user-friendly interface and implemented responsive design.

## **Inventory System Administrator**

Pioneer Hardware (Sep 2021 - Jan 2022)

- Managed and maintained the shop's inventory system to ensure accurate tracking of stock levels and product availability.
- Updated the system with new stock entries, product details, and supplier information, ensuring data integrity.

# **Educational Background**

## **High National Diploma In IT**

Sri Lanka Institute of Advanced Technological Education - Naiwala ATI 2021 - 2024

### **Diploma In Graphic Designing**

Golden Collage Thihariya 2018 - 2019

# **Diploma In English**

Thihariya International School 22021 - 2022

# **Projects**

- Travel Agency Website Built Using WordPress Site Link - <a href="http://agency.wuaze.com/">http://agency.wuaze.com/</a>
- E-Commerce site Built Using WordPress Site link - <a href="http://asmeereshop.great-site.net/">http://asmeereshop.great-site.net/</a>
- Train Block Seat Booking System Built Using PHP, CSS, MYSQL, JS
  Site Link <a href="https://remis.railway.gov.lk/Seat Booking/index.php">https://remis.railway.gov.lk/Seat Booking/index.php</a>
- Hotel Management System Built Using C#, SQL
- Hotel Management Web Application Built Using HTML, CSS, JS, PHP (Laravel Framework), MYSQL

#### Contact

90/D Nasar mawatha, Udugoda, Ruggahawila. +94 723796453 mohamedasmeer325@gmail.com Portfolio || Linkedin || GitHub

# Skills

#### **Technical Skills**

- · WordPress, HTML, CSS, JS
- PHP, JAVA, C#
- Photoshop, Illustrator
- MYSQL
- Laravel
- UI/UX Design

#### Soft Skills

- · Problem solving
- Time management
- Organizational skills
- · Creative thinking
- · Strong commitment

## **Tools/Sofware**

- · Office Software
- · Design Software
- Development Tools
- Digital Marketing Tools:

#### **Certification/Short Courses**

 University of Moratuwa Certified - Web Design, Frond End Web Development, Python For Beginner

# Languages

- English
- Tamil
- Sinhala